American Council for Emigres in the Professions; Records ger017
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP, Undated; 4; originals - 1160 individual files
  - Wertheimer, Otto, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 117)
  - Wetzler, Adolf, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 118)
  - Wiese, Leopold von, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 119)
  - Wilbrandt, Hans, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 120)
  - Wilbur, Walter, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 121)
  - Wild, Grete, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 122)
  - Wilde, Johannes, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 123)
  - Wilga, Jan, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 124)
  - Wilk, Kurt, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 125)
  - Wilks, Wilhelmine, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 126)
  - Wille, Werner, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 127)
  - Willmann, Otto, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 128)
  - Willner, Otto, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 129)
  - Winkler, Wilhelm, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 130)
  - Winterstein, H., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 131)
  - Witte, George de, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 132)
  - Witte, Max, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 133)
  - Wittels, Fritz, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 134)
  - Wohryzek, Walther, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 135)
  - Wolf, Frantisek, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 136)
  - Wolff, Martin, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 137)
  - Wolff, Maurice, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 138)
  - Wolff, Theodore, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 139)
  - Wolff, Werner, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 140)
  - Wolken, Benedikt, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 141)
  - Wollemborg, Leo J., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 142)
  - Wolheim, Ernst 144. Woss, Magda, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 143)
  - Wüllenweber, Walther, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 145)
  - Wunderlich, George M., Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 146)
  - Xirau, Jose Raymond, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 147)
  - Zaglits, Oscar, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 148)
  - Zappler, Marcel, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 149)
  - Zawadowsky, George, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 150)
  - Zeller, Gaston, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 151)
  - Zellner, Hans & Marion, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 152)
  - Zouckermann, Raymond, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 153)
  - American Committee for Émigré Scholars, Writers and Artists, [1938-1940] (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 154)
  - Committee for Work Relief for Refugees, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 155)
  - Petty Cash, Undated (Box 7 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 156)